( WINCH CLICKING )
( BUBBLES POPPING )
( SCREAMING )
( PROJECTOR CLICKS )
This is Andy Barclay .
Eight years ago , he touched off the scandal
that nearly crippled this company ,
claiming that his Good Guy doll , Chucky ,
was possessed by Charles Lee Ray ,
the notorious Lakeshore Strangler .
( PEOPLE MURMURING )
Now I ask you , ladies and gentlemen ,
after all the lawsuits and negative publicity ,
when the company is finally getting back on its feet again ,
where is the wisdom in putting the Good Guy back on the market ?
Mr. Sullivan , before any of this happened ,
the Good Guy outsold all our other toys 2-to-1 .
Even now , interest in the market place is at its peak .
The factory is up and running again .
We should be in stores by next week .
We cannot let the fantasies of one disturbed boy
influence company policy .
Well , what if the doll somehow affects
another child in a negative way ?
You could have a public relations nightmare on your hands .
You know , one of the hardest things about this business
is that it is a business .
It doesn 't matter what we 're selling .
Whether it 's cars , nuclear weapons , or , yes , even toys .
The bottom line is the bottom line .
And what are children , after all , but consumer trainees ?
( ALL CHUCKLING )
Andy Barclay is ancient history .
No one remembers him . Nobody cares .
I have made up my mind .
We 're moving ahead .
Thank you .
WOMAN : Okay . MAN : All right .
Mr. Sullivan .
If there 's nothing I can say to convince you ,
then I must go on record with my position .
I 'm completely against this .
Your position is crystal clear , Miles ,
and you can be sure I won 't forget .
Just a minute , folks ! Please .
Mr. Sullivan , we have a little surprise for you .
The guys at the factory sent this over .
And we all wanted you to have it .
It 's the first one off the assembly line .
The Good Guy of the ' 90s !
( ALL CHEERING )
Well , if there 's nothing else , I 'm gonna get going .
Fine .
PETZOLD : It 's just , my wife 's expecting me .
It 's our anniversary .
Fine , Petzold .
Well , I guess I could review the Larrabee report after dinner .
Good night , Mr. Sullivan .
Good night .
( ELEVATOR BEEPS )
( SIGHS )
( GRUNTING )
( EXHALES )
Well , despite a downdraft in the bond market ,
stocks were able to post a rally on Friday ,
thanks to a couple of different factors .
Not only did the stronger-than-expected employment report
allay some recession fears ,
but also there was a technical rebound in stock ,
short covering , program buying ,
and the resurgence in the deal stocks
help set the tone for rally on the Street .
Here 's a look at the numbers now .
For Friday , the Dow Industrial 's up sixteen and two-thirds .
Of the highs of the day ,
the transportation average up a little better than three .
Utilities bouncing up a point to pass at 12 , at 22 , 61 , 78 .
SP 500 Cash are better than two
with the margin peaking up almost two and a half
with the premier ending at 1.59 .
New York Stock Exchange Index up 1.23 ,
volume backing off a bit at 164 million shares .
Advances beat declines just about
9 - to-5 on the New York Stock Exchange .
The up volume 103 million shares , the down volume ...
( MAN CONTINUES ON TV )
In just a moment 's time ...
( MUTTERS )
( GRUNTING )
Where is it ?
Ah .
Phew !
MAN : ... bonds headed south on the stronger-than-expected economic data ,
which served to bolster the U.S. dollar .
The Dollar Index up a quarter point .
( GROANING )
( MAN CONTINUES SPEAKING ON TV )
( SCREAMING )
( GROANING )
( SIREN WAILING )
( TIRES SCREECHING )
( TRAIN WHISTLE BLOWING )
( RATTLING )
( WHIRRING )
( GRUNTING )
DOLL 1 : Hi , my name is Larry .
DOLL 2 : Hi , my name is Pauly .
Hey , wanna play ?
I like to be hugged .
Hi , my name is Larry .
Hi , my name is Pauly .
Hey , wanna play ?
I like to be hugged .
Hi , my name is Larry .
Hi , my name is Pauly .
Hey , wanna play ?
I like to be ... ( DOLLS STOP TALKING )
( SCREAMS )
( WHIMPERS )
( CHUCKY LAUGHING )
Don 't fuck with the Chuck !
Oh , my God .
( SULLIVAN GROANS )
( GROANS )
Bull 's-eye !
( GRUNTING )
( GROANS ) ( SCREAMING )
( SCREAMING )
( CHOKING )
Just like the good old days .
Nothing like a strangulation to get the circulation going .
You 're my only ticket out of here , Andy .
I got to get out of this goddamn body .
Where are you , you little shit ?
( DRILL INSTRUCTOR YELLING INDISTINCTLY )
Inward , hut !
DE SILVA : Come on . Come on , yeah ! You can do it !
Come on . You can do it , Jackson , hurry up .
Yeah ! Move . Yes !
Come on . Let 's go . Yeah ! Come on .
Get moving ! Go to the end of the line !
COCHRANE : I see that for the past eight years
you 've been in one foster home after another .
Mind if I ask why ?
They took me away from my mother .
She 's under special care .
I know that .
I meant how come you never got settled anywhere ?
Adjustment problems .
I can read , Barclay .
I 'm asking you .
I never felt comfortable with those people .
They weren 't family , they were strangers .
All right , listen up , Barclay .
I 'm willing to cut you some slack because you 've had it so rough ,
but you 're a troublemaker .
And I got a real problem with troublemakers .
They don 't fit into the system .
So here 's my advice .
Grow up , you 're not a kid anymore .
It 's time to forget these fantasies of killer dolls .
Yes , sir .
" When I was a child , I thought as a child .
" But when I became a man , I put away childish things . "
First Corinthians .
Look alive , Barclay , on your feet !
At Kent , we take bedwetters and turn them into men .
( ELECTRIC RAZOR BUZZES )
Oh , yes . Yes .
Oh , yes !
We 're seeing some skin now , aren 't we ?
Presto ! You 're bald .
( CHUCKLES )
Always feels a little weird at first .
Next .
( TV PLAYING )
( VIDEO GAME BEEPING )
( LAUGHS )
Kiss it goodbye .
You know , the Romans invented the military cut .
You know why ?
Why ?
To keep their hair short
so their enemies couldn 't grab ahold of it in battle
and slit their throat .
( LAUGHS )
Now , hold still .
Oh , shit .
( CHUCKLES )
BOY ON TV : We 're back , and we 're better than ever .
No one will play with me .
Uh-oh . There 's a friend in need .
Hey , cheer up !
BOY : Who are you ?
I 'm a Good Guy .
( ECHOING ) Good Guy ! Good Guy ! Good Guy ! Good Guy !
I 've just come from the Good Guy Clubhouse ,
and I 'll be your friend till the end .
BOY : You will ?
Wow !
Sure I will .
BOTH : Hidey-ho !
So , all aboard for high-flying fun with me , your friend till the end ,
the Good Guy doll from Play Pals .
BOY : Come on , man !
( THUDDING )
( BANGING )
Are you okay ?
The bastards ! Fucking bastards !
What happened ?
Shelton , that 's what happened .
Shelton and his goddamn lackeys .
Thank you . I 'm fine .
I 'm Andy .
You must be new .
Otherwise you 'd know they don 't tolerate any form of individuality here .
Certainly nothing so personal as the first name .
Yeah , right , I forgot . Barclay .
( SIGHS ) Whitehurst . Harold Aubrey for the record .
So , who 's this Shelton ?
Cadet Lieutenant Colonel Brett C. Shelton .
He 's God around here .
Don 't expect any mercy from him .
( SIGHS ) Welcome to hell , Barclay .
All present and accounted for , sir .
Thank you , Major Ellis .
You 're the new boy , huh ?
Yeah .
How you doing ?
Pretty good . Good .
Who said you could look at me ?
( YELLS ) Do you know who I am ?
Shelton ?
That 's Lieutenant Colonel Shelton to you , asshole !
Lieutenant Colonel Shelton .
No . Lieutenant Colonel Shelton ,
sir .
Lieutenant Colonel Shelton , sir .
What 's your name , dipweed ?
Barclay .
Sir . Louder .
Sir ! Louder !
( LOUDLY ) Sir ! Louder !
( YELLS ) Sir !
That 's much better , new boy . That 's much better .
Shit , Whitehurst . ( SNICKERS )
You are without a doubt
the most pathetic thing I have ever seen !
Wouldn 't you agree ?
I asked you a question , nimrod !
No , sir ! I don 't agree , sir !
Are you contradicting me , you sorry-ass sack of shit ?
You asshole .
What did you say ?
I said , " You asshole , " sir !
You think you 're pretty funny , don 't you , De Silva ?
Yes , I do , sir .
Why don 't you drop and give me 25 right now ?
Twenty-five what , sir ?
Twenty-five push-ups , De Silva .
One , sir . Two , sir ...
Now , you women might think that
because you 're so much more delicate ,
you deserve some sort of special treatment ,
and once a month we 're just going to get on out of your way .
DE SILVA : Twelve , sir . Thirteen , sir .
Well , you can forget it .
The same rules apply for everybody .
DE SILVA : Eighteen , sir . Nineteen , sir .
SHELTON : Only the fittest survive .
DE SILVA : Twenty-two , sir . Twenty-three , sir .
One-handed .
Twenty-four , sir .
Twenty-five , sir .
Recover .
( EXHALES )
How you doing , Tyler ?
Sorry . Nothing from your dad today . Maybe tomorrow .
Listen , he 's busy flying jets , defending the country .
He 'll write to you when he gets the chance .
I know .
Hey !
I got a job for you .
Would you give this to the new kid for me ? Barclay .
Yes , sir .
Attaboy .
Whoa .
Watch it , kid ! Anyway , how could you be so stupid ?
Hey , look out !
( DOOR SHUTS )
A Good Guy .
( SCREAMS ) ( EXCLAIMS )
Who the fuck are you ?
I thought you guys only said three sentences .
I 'm new and improved .
I never saw a doll like you before .
All right , kid , fun 's over .
Where the hell 's Andy ?
Andy ?
Can 't you read ?
He was supposed to get this package .
Tampering with the mail is a federal offense .
Sorry . Is he your best friend ?
He 's more than that . He 's my new lease on life .
Wait a minute .
I got a new body ,
and I ain 't told anyone about my little secret yet .
So , what 's your name , kid ?
Tyler . What 's yours ?
Chucky . But , uh ,
my real name is Charles Lee Ray .
( GUNS FIRING )
Whitehurst , what am I doing wrong ?
( BOTH CHUCKLING )
Is there anything you can 't do ?
Yeah . I can 't seem to get thrown out of this place .
Barclay , meet De Silva .
Hi . Hi .
So , want to show me ?
Yeah , sure . Okay .
( SIGHS )
No . Put the elbow ... Yeah , like that .
And like this .
No . Keep both eyes open .
Keep your sights on the target .
Now hold your breath .
Squeeze the trigger , don 't pull it .
( FIRES GUN )
You 're not concentrating .
You know , it was really great what you did for us back there at formation .
Well , Shelton 's a major dick .
( LAUGHS ) Tell me about it .
( GUN FIRES )
TYLER : Couldn 't we just play hide-and-seek ?
CHUCKY : Hold still .
TYLER : What do you call this game anyway ?
Hide the Soul . Trust me . You 're gonna love it .
Whatever you say , Charles .
( CHANTING )
Give me the power , I beg of you !
( THUNDER RUMBLING )
( CONTINUES CHANTING )
( DOOR OPENS ) MAJOR : Yes , sir .
COCHRANE : So we divide the troops in half ,
that 'll be about 70 on each team . Shit !
Charles , stop swearing .
Per soldier , and we 're gonna need
the Springfield 0-3s ... Yes , sir .
... marked for both the red team and the blue team .
What are you doing , Tyler ?
We 're playing Hide the Soul .
I 'll catch up with you .
I 'll start loading the paint pellet .
We don 't play with dolls , do we now , Tyler ?
Dolls are for girls .
But Charles is my new best friend .
Tyler , you know better than to talk back to a superior officer .
Yes , sir .
Clean that up .
I 'll take care of this .
I 'll be back !
( THUD )
Left ! Left ! Left , right , left !
Left ! Left !
Get that weapon up , Barclay !
Platoon , halt !
Left face !
New boy , fall out !
( YELLS ) Fall out !
SHELTON : Order , hut !
Port , arms !
Right shoulder , arms !
Left shoulder , arms !
Port , arms !
Right shoulder , arms !
( GARBLED COMMANDS )
Barclay !
It 's not a baton , Barclay .
( SNICKERS )
You look like a goddamn majorette over here .
I 'm not used to guns , sir .
( SCOFFS )
Does this look like a gun to you , Barclay ?
It 's a rifle !
Major Ellis ? Sir !
Would you please show the new boy the difference ?
This is my rifle , this is my gun .
This is for shooting , and this is for fun .
A soldier 's rifle is his best friend .
Remember that .
Stop !
Shit !
CHUCKY : Help ! Please , mister !
Please , somebody !
Jesus !
CHUCKY : I 'm stuck ! Mister !
I 'm in here !
Hold on . I 'm coming ! ( CHUCKY SCREAMING )
Where are you ?
I 'm coming .
Yell or something ! Make a noise !
Where are you ?
What the ...
( GASPS )
Oh , my God .
No ! Stop !
( LAUGHING EVILLY )
Stop !
( SCREAMING )
SHELTON : Fall out .
You get back there .
Better finish unpacking , Barclay .
Shelton 's notorious for surprise inspections .
What are you doing ?
What does it look like ? I 'm polishing Shelton 's shoes .
He makes you polish his shoes ?
No , I offered out of the kindness of my heart .
Whitehurst , did you see Cochrane with that doll today ?
No . What doll ?
He was carrying a Good Guy doll ,
just before the accident with the garbage truck .
Good Guys , I remember those .
Yeah , me , too .
( SPITS )
Uh , lights out in a few minutes .
I 'm going to go get washed up .
( DOOR OPENS )
( DOOR CLOSES )
Barclay , I almost forgot .
Sergeant Clark wanted to know if you got that package .
What package ?
He said you got a package in the mail .
That little kid Tyler was supposed to bring it to you .
Didn 't you get it ? No .
Who would 've sent me a package ?
( GROANS )
Hey , long time no see , pal .
No , you 're dead . We killed you !
You know what they say ,
you just can 't keep a Good Guy down .
( LAUGHING )
Andy , how you 've grown .
You 're not gonna kill me . You need me .
You need to transfer your soul into my body .
Wrong again , wimp .
I got some fresh meat lined up
and I 'm not gonna let you spoil it , not this time .
( GASPS ) Tyler .
Yeah , just think . Chucky 's gonna be a bro .
( LAUGHING EVILLY )
I 'm not gonna let you get away with this .
I 'm not gonna let you near that kid .
( EXCLAIMS )
( GRUNTING )
( LAUGHING )
What 's the matter , Barclay , huh ? You homesick ?
You miss your mommy ?
What the fuck is this ?
I 'm sorry about your shoe , all right . I 'll polish it .
Just give me back the doll .
No , no , you listen to me .
You tell Whitehurst he 's off the hook , huh ?
I got myself another slave .
And clean up this mess . You got five demerits .
What about the doll ?
Ah . My kid sister 's birthday is coming up .
I think she 's gonna love it , don 't you ?
( DOOR CREAKING )
( DOOR CREAKS )
( RUSTLING )
( GRUNTING )
Oh , shit .
Andy .
What the fuck ?
No , stop !
What the fuck are you doing in my room , Barclay ?
You wouldn 't believe me .
Where 's the doll , Barclay ?
Where 's the fucking doll ?
You took it , didn 't you ? No !
What 's going on ?
Yeah , well , somebody sure as hell took it .
( THUNDER RUMBLING )
It 's almost midnight , Colonel .
Is this really necessary ?
I 'm trying to weed out a thief , sir .
You 've always told me how important it is
to uphold the school 's code of honor .
I 'm simply trying to impress that upon the men , sir .
All right , Shelton , make your point .
But I want everybody back inside at 0100 hours .
Yes , sir .
By the time we get through with Barclay ,
he 's going to be living in a whole world full of shit .
All right . We 've only got an hour , so let 's make it count .
Yes , sir .
ELLIS : All right , ladies , get those weapons in the air .
I want to see ' em high !
Higher !
I think I 'm gonna throw up .
CADET 1 : You 're dead , new boy .
CADET 2 : Fucking geek .
( FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING )
CHUCKY : " Dear Charles , you 're it .
" Come and find me , your best friend . "
Shit .
TYLER : Charles .
Come and find me !
God damn it .
Platoon ! ALL : Hut !
Double time !
ALL : Hut !
Get those knees up , ladies !
Whitehurst , where do the kids sleep ?
Above the portico . Why ?
ELLIS : You 're wearing combat boots , not ballet slippers .
Come on , move ! Barclay ?
ELLIS : It 's gonna get a lot worse than this !
Get the lead out . Come on , move it !
Faster , faster . Let 's go , Brock !
Get those knees in the sky ! Come on !
( GROANING )
You son of a bitch !
( CHUCKLES )
You got a hell of a punch there , Barclay .
Now I 'll see what kind of tough guy you really are .
Get your head around .
( GIGGLES )
Tyler , come out , come out , wherever you are .
Olly olly oxen free .
Get out here , you little son of a bitch .
ELLIS : Three ! ALL : Three !
ELLIS : You 're not sounding off .
ALL : Four !
ELLIS : You 're pissing me off !
ALL : Five !
All right , Barclay , you got me curious .
What are you trying to prove ?
Forget it .
No , really , I want to know .
All right .
The doll 's alive . He 's after Tyler .
You 're right , forget it .
I just hope he can take care of himself .
DE SILVA : ( WHISPERING ) Come on . IVERS : Okay , okay .
( SHUSHING ) Quiet .
( BOTH GASP )
( BOTH LAUGHING )
Shut up .
Okay , come on .
Come on .
I can 't believe I let you talk me into this .
Okay , just stay here and keep an eye out , okay ?
Oh , I live for this .
I know , Ivers . Now , go , go !
( SHUSHING )
You know , I don 't see what you see in that guy , anyway .
I don 't know , he 's ... Well , he 's just different from everybody else .
Oh , please .
Oh , he 's kind of cute , too .
Mmm . ( LAUGHS )
Okay .
Foster homes . No wonder he 's so quiet .
( THUMPING ) ( BOTH GASP )
What was that ?
( BOTH LAUGHING )
So you took the doll ?
Shelton will have you court-martialed if he finds out .
We 're playing Hide and Seek . What are you guys doing ?
We couldn 't sleep .
( GASPS ) Oh , he is so cute .
Ivers , he was mine first ! Give him back ! Give him back !
( SHUSHING ) You guys , please be quiet .
Can you go stand guard ?
Yes , sir .
So what 's his name ?
Ask him yourself . All right .
What is your name , little doll ?
Hi , I 'm Chucky . And I 'm your friend to the end .
Hidey-ho ! ( LAUGHS )
( LAUGHS ) I love it .
His real name is Charles Lee Ray .
Oh , is that so ? Give me your lipstick .
What for ? Just give it to me .
Oh , no .
What are you doing ?
DE SILVA : You 'll see .
Wait . Stop .
Here you go , little baby ! TYLER : Come on !
You 're messing him up .
Oh , you 're so cute .
Aw . TYLER : Don 't do that !
Don 't . He looks stupid .
You 're making him look like a wuss .
No , he looks sweet . What are you doing ?
( DISTANT CLANGING )
You guys , someone 's coming .
Come on , let 's go .
Come on . Let 's go . Wait , wait .
TYLER : Stop ! What about Charles ?
( EXCLAIMS )
This means war .
( SOFT CLATTERING )
What the hell ?
I like to be hugged . ( EXCLAIMS )
( LAUGHS )
( CLATTERING )
( SCREAMING )
( GASPING )
( GROANING )
Oh , you got to be fucking kidding me !
( GASPING )
A man lives through two tours in Nam
and then one night he just drops dead .
Doesn 't make any sense .
( REVEILLE PLAYING )
SHELTON : At ease !
We will now take a moment of silence
to honor Colonel Cochrane .
He was a fine man and he will be sorely missed .
Bow your heads for prayer .
SHELTON : Take seats !
It 's getting pretty shaggy , Carlson .
I want to see you on Friday .
Yes , sir .
( GROANS ) Monday , Fabrizzio .
( GRUNTS ) Yes , sir .
My man .
( EXCLAIMS ) Tuesday .
Look at you , Whitehurst . You 're a disgrace .
When 's the last time you had a trim ?
Two weeks ago , Sergeant , I think .
You think ? You think ?
I want to see you right after breakfast . You got it ?
Yes , sir , Sergeant Botnick , sir .
And what are you looking at , new boy ?
Wednesday .
Barclay , what are you doing ?
You can 't just get up in the middle of mess .
( ALL LAUGHING )
( MOUTHING ) Shut up .
Major .
At ease !
( VIDEO GAME BEEPING )
Tyler .
Hi , Barclay . What 's up ?
I gotta talk to you about Chucky .
You mean Charles .
Have you seen him ?
Not since last night .
He 's hiding somewhere .
He 's gonna lay low till he knows you 're alone ,
and then he 's gonna come after you .
He just wants to play .
Listen to me , Tyler .
No matter what he says , no matter what he promises you ,
you 've got to stay away from him .
Don 't let him fool you . He 's bad .
Charles isn 't bad . He 's a Good Guy .
It says so on his shirt .
He lies , Tyler .
Believe me , he 's bad news .
He 's hurt a lot of people .
I think Colonel Cochrane was one of them .
You 're just jealous ' cause he 's my best friend now , instead of yours .
( VIDEO GAME BEEPING )
Look , you better keep this .
( BUZZING )
Whitehurst , you are without a doubt
the sorriest excuse for a soldier to ever disgrace these walls .
Face it , you 're not cut out for this life .
Why don 't you do yourself a favor
and get the hell out of Kent ?
If I had any choice in the matter , I would , sir .
Smart-ass .
Presto ! You 're bald .
( CHUCKLES )
( SNIFFLES ) Yeah .
( WHISTLING TUNE )
What the hell ?
How did you get in there ?
That haircut ain 't regulation , soldier .
When 's the last time you had a trim , huh ?
( LAUGHING )
Kiss it goodbye .
( BUZZING )
( LAUGHING )
Presto ! You 're dead .
( CHUCKY LAUGHING EVILLY )
It 's definitely you .
I just forgot my ... My ...
Boo ! ( GASPS )
The annual war games
have been an unbroken tradition here at Kent for over 50 years .
Colonel Cochrane was a man who believed in the value of tradition .
He not only would have wanted us to go on ,
he 'd have ordered us to go on .
Therefore , the war games will proceed as scheduled .
( ALL YELLING )
Lieutenant Colonel Shelton will command the blue team .
Major Rawlings will head up the reds .
The objective is simple .
To capture the other team 's flag ,
bring it back here safely to base .
Rawlings .
You will pick up your weapons in the armory before moving out .
You will be using the standard issue Springfield 0-3 .
Your ammo .
( FIRING )
Shelton .
If you get hit , you are dead .
Hike back to base .
Commanders , take charge of your teams .
May the best team win .
Good luck , men and women .
Nice of you to join us .
( PANTS NERVOUSLY )
Looks like Botnick 's in a pretty bad mood today .
What 's wrong ?
Nothing . Nothing 's wrong .
Nothing 's wrong . I 'm fine . Nothing 's wrong .
This ought to slow the pricks down .
INSTRUCTOR : Left ! Left ! Left !
INSTRUCTOR : ( SINGING ) Here we go again
CADETS : ( SINGING ) Here we go again
Same old stuff again
Marching down the avenue
Two more miles , we 'll be through
I 'll be getting rid of you
Same old ugly stuff
Here we go again
Marching down the avenue
One more mile , we 'll be through
I 'll be getting rid of you
What 's going on , Whitehurst ?
You saw something , didn 't you ? You saw Chucky .
Don 't wimp out on me now , Whitehurst .
I need your help . That kid needs your help .
I didn 't see anything , okay ?
I didn 't see anything at all .
INSTRUCTOR : Your left , right , your left
CADETS : Your left , right , your left
Your military left
Ellis , let 's make sure the perimeters are secured .
Yes , sir .
She checks all the windows ,
and then the babysitter hears this thump , thump .
Thumping .
Like something 's being dragged across the floor upstairs .
And suddenly she thinks , " I haven 't checked on the children . "
So she hurries to the top of the stairs ,
and when she gets there ,
she sees her boyfriend , completely dismembered ,
dragging himself across the floor by his chin .
Thump . Slide .
Thump . Slide . CADET 1 : Ugh !
( CADET 2 LAUGHS )
Thump . Slide .
IVERS : That is gross .
( DE SILVA LAUGHING )
Hey , you guys , I got a better story and it 's true .
It 's about this mental institution ,
and it 's a few miles away from here .
Hey !
Hope it wasn 't something I said .
( CHUCKLES ) No . I 'm sorry .
De Silva , where do you think the red team 's camped out ?
Could be anywhere .
Shelton 'll find them . He always does .
By the way , you can call me Kristin .
What ?
Kristin .
It 's my first name . Do you have one ?
Andy . Oh .
Come on , Andy , I want to show you something .
Pretty cool , huh ?
Yeah .
BARCLAY : I almost forgot there were places like that .
People just go to have fun .
( TWIGS CRACKLING ) Listen !
Somebody 's out there .
It 's probably just a chipmunk or something .
Nothing scares you , does it ?
No .
Man , I really gotta get out of this body .
I 'm going after Tyler .
Are you crazy ? You 'll never find them .
Wanna bet ?
I swiped this from Shelton 's tent .
He sent out a reconnaissance mission right before we pitched camp .
The red team is somewhere around here .
That kid 's a sitting duck , Whitehurst .
Now , are you with me or not ?
I 'm sorry , I can 't .
ELLIS : Up and at ' em , ladies , we 're moving out !
I want this camp to be a ghost town in five minutes !
I thought we weren 't going until dawn , sir .
Someone stole the reconnaissance map out of the Colonel 's tent ,
so we 're making our move now .
Get going , Hanley .
Whitehurst .
You wouldn 't know anything about a missing map , would you ?
Where the hell 's Barclay ? Whitehurst !
Colonel Shelton , you 'd better have a look in here , sir .
( SIGHS )
What is it , Ellis ?
Barclay 's gone AWOL , sir .
( SCOFFS )
He stole the map .
That little fucking traitor 's doubling for the reds .
Where 's Tyler ?
He went AWOL with some guy named Charles .
Where 's Andy ?
Whitehurst , where is he ?
SHELTON : Platoon , halt !
All right . De Silva , you 're going to take the right flank .
Siegel , you take the left . I want you to check in
on the radio every five minutes .
Yes , sir . All right , move it .
The rest of us are gonna spread out
and meet up with Ellis at Split Rock .
Move out !
Whitehurst , move !
Thanks for coming after me .
What are friends for ?
Duck .
That was a close one .
Now , we can play Hide the Soul .
I 'm tired . I don 't want to play that dumb game anymore .
You 're a fucking drag , you know that ?
Watch your mouth , Charles .
Stop calling me that !
What 's the knife for ?
A good soldier is always prepared , Tyler .
Barclay was right . You 're not a Good Guy .
( CHUCKLES ) Sorry , kid , you got me . I 'm bad .
Now , assume the position .
TYLER : No ! ( CHUCKY GROANS )
Get back here !
Barclay ! Barclay !
Tyler !
( TWIG SNAPS )
Barclay , you fucking traitor , give me my map !
Listen to me , Shelton !
You got any idea what we do to traitors , Barclay ?
Tyler 's in trouble .
Come on , Whitehurst , back me up .
Major Ellis , call in the flanks .
Yes , sir .
De Silva , Siegel , do you copy ?
De Silva , do you copy ?
ELLIS ON RADIO : De Silva , come in .
( SCREAMING )
Siegel 's on his way back , sir .
No word yet from De Silva .
Well , keep trying . Yes , sir .
TYLER : Help ! Help !
Tyler !
Barclay !
Are you okay , Tyler ?
Well , looks like we got ourselves a little POW .
Barclay , you were right . Charles is bad .
He tried to hurt me .
Who the hell 's Charles ?
CHUCKY ON RADIO : Come in , Barclay . Come in .
Who the hell is that ?
It 's Charles .
Who is this ?
CHUCKY : Put Barclay on , jarhead .
ELLIS : It 's the reds . They 're up to something .
What do you want ?
CHUCKY : I want the kid .
Bring him up to the old jeep or there 'll be hell to pay .
DE SILVA : Andy , don 't do it ! De Silva !
You hear that , Barclay ?
BARCLAY : Don 't touch her , you son of a bitch .
Now , bring me the kid or I 'll waste her .
Red team , red team . Come in , red team .
CADET : This is red team . Over .
CHUCKY : We got a situation up here at the old jeep .
Blue team sighted . Advise you to move your troops in .
CHUCKY : I hope they like the taste of lead .
Now just sit back and watch the sparks fly .
All right , you two are going to go on up ahead , draw ' em out .
The rest of us are gonna circle around .
Shelton , this is no game .
I 'm telling you , this guy is dangerous .
Relax , Barclay . It 's only paint .
All right . Let 's do it .
I 'm scared , Barclay .
Yeah , me , too .
All right , kid . Get over here !
No .
Don 't fuck with me !
I 'll blow all of you to pieces !
Beat it .
Now , just get down and shut up .
Yeah .
( GUNS FIRING )
Ow !
Hold your fire !
CADET : Hold your fire !
De Silva , where the hell is everybody ?
Hi , soldier .
( LAUGHING )
Fuck me .
( GUNS FIRING )
All right !
( LAUGHING )
Shit !
Stay down ! ( GUNS FIRING )
They 're using live rounds !
( CACKLING )
Hold your fire ! Hold your fire !
Hold your fire !
Oh , God , he 's not breathing . Get away from him !
You did this , didn 't you ?
You sick son of a bitch !
Now I 'm gonna kill you !
Stop it ! Get off of him !
He didn 't do it ! Stop it !
Let go of me . Stop it !
Sayonara , suckers .
DE SILVA : No ! Get off of him !
Stop it ! He didn 't do it !
BARCLAY : Let go of me . DE SILVA : He didn 't do it ! Stop !
Look out !
( EXPLOSION )
IVERS : No ! Oh , my God , what happened ?
It 's Whitehurst .
GIRL : Oh , my God ! Ellis ! Ellis , what happened ?
Epstein , what the hell happened ?
I don 't know . Who fucked with the rifles ?
EPSTEIN : I don 't know . ELLIS : Okay , okay .
Get Clark on the radio . Yes , sir .
And get me a medic up here right now ! Yes , sir .
All right . Everybody stay calm !
( SOBBING )
Epstein , I want that radio ! Oh , God .
( CARNIVAL MUSIC PLAYING )
( PEOPLE SCREAMING )
( LOUD ROCK MUSIC PLAYING ON STEREO )
SECURITY GUARD : This is the last time I 'm gonna tell you .
Give that thing a rest or you 're out of here , both of you .
Come on , we 're not bothering anybody .
You 're bothering me . Keep it down .
( MUSIC STOPS )
GIRL : Jeez !
Mister , mister , you 've got to help me .
What 's wrong ? What 's the matter ?
Charles ! Charles , he 's after me .
Who 's Charles ? He 's a Good Guy .
He wants to play Hide the Soul . Okay , slow down , slow down !
Have a seat over there . Are you from Kent ?
Yes , sir . What 's your name , son ?
Ronald Tyler . Private first-class , sir .
Have a seat . How about some gum , Private ?
I know how it must hurt when a friend does something bad to you .
Sure does .
But I bet your friend ... What 's his name , Charles ?
I bet you Charles didn 't mean it .
I bet you he 's really sorry .
No , he isn 't . He wants to hurt me .
Nobody 's going to hurt you .
Hey , I know what will cheer you up .
Look what I found .
MAN : Here 's your prize . There you go .
Thank you , Daddy .
Let 's go in the Super Loop .
CHILDREN : Yeah .
Hey , maybe somebody 's seen him .
Oh , God .
Come on . Wait .
( PEOPLE SCREAMING )
Mommy , Mommy , I loved it !
Were you scared ? BOTH : No !
Let 's have some popcorn and go on one more ride .
CHUCKY : Perfect . In there .
Don 't even think about it .
Come on . Okay .
In there !
( BELL TOLLING )
( CREAKING )
( LAUGHING )
( DEMONIC LAUGHTER )
( THUNDER RUMBLING )
CHUCKY : Time to play .
This looks good . Park it .
( BELL TOLLING )
Ah !
( CACKLING ) Whoa !
( GRUNTING )
( DEMONIC LAUGHTER )
( SCREAMS )
Kid !
( SKELETON CACKLING )
( DEMONIC LAUGHTER )
( SCREAMS )
Ha !
Tyler !
Barclay ! Barclay ! In here !
He 's got a gun !
( GUN FIRING )
Kid !
( SCREAMING )
( LAUGHS )
Are you okay ? Oh , my God .
( SOBBING ) Oh , God .
Here . Take it .
You can do it .
I 'll be okay .
( STEAM WHOOSHING )
( ROARING )
( GRUNTING )
( YELLING )
Help ! Help !
Yeah ! You 're mine now , Tyler !
( ROARING )
CHUCKY : No !
( SCREAMING )
( PEOPLE SCREAMING )
Tyler !
Barclay !
Tyler , watch out !
Shit !
( TURBINE WHIRRING )
( PEOPLE SCREAMING )
This is it , kid ! End of the line .
( CHANTING )
Give me the power , I beg of you !
( THUNDER RUMBLING )
( CHUCKY CHANTING )
Come on , keep both eyes open . Hold your breath .
( CHUCKY SCREAMING )
( CONTINUES CHANTING )
( SCREAMING )
Yeah !
Are you okay ?
Yeah .
Come on , let 's get out of here .
( GRUNTING )
( SCREAMING )
Hold on , Tyler ! Hold on !
CHUCKY : Give me the fucking kid ! He 's mine !
TYLER : Help ! He 's mine !
Give me the fucking kid !
BARCLAY : Hold on , Tyler . Hold on .
He 's mine !
BARCLAY : Come on , hold on , Tyler . TYLER : Barclay !
TYLER : Here . Take the knife !
CHUCKY : Give him to me !
TYLER : Take it ! Here , take it !
Barclay ! Hold on !
TYLER : Reach for it ! CHUCKY : He 's mine !
No !
( SCREAMING )
Tyler , come on . I got you .
Okay , we 're on our way in .
DISPATCHER : Roger .
You 'll have to come with us now , son .
Are you going to be okay ?
Don 't worry . I 've been here before .
Watch your head .
( SIREN WAILING )